export const data = [
    {
        question: '¿Pregunta 1?',
        choices: ['opcion1', 'opcion2', 'opcion3', 'opcion4'],
        answer: 'opcion1',
    },
    
    {
        question: '¿Pregunta 2?',
        choices: ['opcion1', 'opcion2', 'opcion3', 'opcion4'],
        answer: 'opcion2',
    },

    {
        question: '¿Pregunta 3?',
        choices: ['opcion1', 'opcion2', 'opcion3', 'opcion4'],
        answer:'opcion2',
    },

    {
        question: '¿Pregunta 4?',
        choices: ['opcion1', 'opcion2', 'opcion3', 'opcion4'],
        answer: 'opcion3',
    },

    {
        question: '¿Pregunta 5?',
        choices: ['opcion1', 'opcion2', 'opcion3', 'opcion4'],
        answer: 'opcion4',
    },

    {
        question: '¿Pregunta 6?',
        choices: ['opcion1', 'opcion2', 'opcion3', 'opcion4'],
        answer: 'opcion2',
    },

    {
        question: '¿Pregunta 7?',
        choices: ['opcion1', 'opcion2', 'opcion3', 'opcion4'],
        answer: 'opcion2',
    },

    {
        question: '¿Pregunta 8?',
        choices: ['opcion1', 'opcion2', 'opcion3', 'opcion4'],
        answer:'opcion1',
    },

    {
        question: '¿Pregunta 9?',
        choices: ['opcion1', 'opcion2', 'opcion3', 'opcion4'],
        answer: 'opcion3',
    },

    {
        question: '¿Pregunta 10?',
        choices: ['opcion1', 'opcion2', 'opcion3', 'opcion4'],
        answer: 'opcion1',
    }
];
